

**NUR AMIRA BT JUHAN** 

#### EXPERIENCE & BACKGROUND

Coming from Hospitality background with various experience and knowledge with good interpersonal skills and know how to make an effective communication.

Graduated with Bachelor Degree in Culinary Art Management has taught me a lot about problem solving skills and critical thinking. Have an experience in a 5 star hotel, as back and front of the house staff and business development study and as Business Support Administrator in AXA Affin General Insurance.

#### **CONTACT INFO**

Address : No. 98, Jalan Seri Emas 58,

Taman Seri Telok Emas, 75460, Telok Mas,

Melaka.

Contact Number (Mobile) : 019-6861990

Email ID : <u>nuramirajuhan@hotmail.com</u>

#### PERSONAL PARTICULARS

Age : 23 Years Old

Date of Birth : 24 July 1990

Nationality : Malaysia

Gender : Female

Bumiputera : Yes

Marital Status : Single

IC Number : 900724-04-5444

### EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

### **Highest Education**

Education : Local University Certificate

Certificate : Degree

Area of Study : BACHELOR (HONS) Qualification

Type : 2nd Class Upper

Institution : University Technology of MARA (UiTM)

Graduation Date : July 2013

Country : Malaysia

Duration Course : 3 years

CGPA : 3.03

**Second Highest Education** 

Education : Local University Certificate

Certificate : Diploma

Area of Study : Culinary Arts

Graduation Date : June 2011

Country : Malaysia

Duration Course/ : 2 years

CGPA : 3.05

### **COURSE SUBJECTS**

Principles & Practices Of Management	Procurement
Principles & Practices Of Marketing	Presentation Skills
Business & Communication Management	Fundamental Of Hospitality And Tourism Industry
Human Resource Management	Organizational Behavior
Entrepreneurship	Food Purchasing And Cost Control

# WORK EXPERIENCES

No.	Employer	Position	Duration	Job Description
1.	Renaissance Hotel, Melaka	Trainee in Pastry, Asian, Malay, Cold, Butcher Kitchen.	December 2009 – March 2010	Handle big number of customers and events.
2.	Bayview Hotel, Melaka	Trainee in Pastry kitchen	December 2010- March 2011	Preparing large number of pastry products for buffet and hotel events.
3.	AXA Affin General Insurance	Business Support Administrator	September 2013 – Present	Issue policy for Foreign Worker Compensation Scheme. Using AS400 system key in all the data and related cases regarding policy.

## LANGUAGES

Language	Spoken	Written
Bahasa Malaysia	Excellent	Excellent
English	Very Good	Very Good
French	Basic	Basic

## REFERENCES

1. Name : Carol Lazaroo

Contact Number : 012 – 2225324

Position : Department Executive

Company : AXA Affin General Insurance

2. Name : Izzat B. Zulkifly

Contact Number : 017-2901525

Position : Lecturer

Institution : UiTM

3. Name : Zain B Kutut

Contact Number : 016-6274619

Position : Lecturer

Institution : UiTM